https://rmhcharlottesville.org/privacy-policy/

MenuMenuHomeAbout Us
Our MissionOur HistoryOur PeopleMcDonald's PartnershipMedical Community PartnershipEmploymentContact Us
What We Do
Ronald McDonald HouseHow to StayGrants
Get Involved
VolunteerRed Shoe CvilleMeals from the HeartWish ListLove Sandwich ProgramHouse LibraryHospitality Cart Program
Support Us
DonateFundraise for UsPop TabsAdopt the HouseDonate Your VehicleCorporate DonorsLegacy Planning
RMHC BlogEvents
Virginia Gingerbread Christmas2019 Golf Classic at Spring Creek2019 Rotary Golf Tournament at Lakeview2019 Rising Stars
Search for:
HOW TO STAY
DONATE
Privacy Policy
Ronald McDonald House Charities of Charlottesville is pleased to provide information to all of its supporters and guest families regarding our online privacy policy. Please be assured that RMHC uses its best efforts to protect the privacy of visitors to this Web site.
Types of Information Collected and How It Is Used
RMHC gathers personal information, such as first and last names, home addresses, e-mail addresses and credit card numbers, only when voluntarily submitted by you. If you make an online donation, personal information will be collected from you in order to process that donation. The software used to process any credit card transaction has internet security verification to ensure that your credit card is not at risk of being compromised.
With your permission, we will use personal information collected from you to send you information, such as RMHC updates regarding happenings around our House, events, fundraisers and opportunities to support RMHC. If you do not elect to receive such materials, we will not send them to you.
Security of Donor Information
Donor information is stored within a donor management database within RMHC.
Access to the database is restricted to personnel with legitimate business need to access or modify the information contained therein.
Sharing of Personal Information
Companies may be engaged by RMHC to perform a variety of functions, such as assisting with donation collection, providing technical services for our Internet sites, etc. Such companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform certain functions. However, these companies may use such personal information only for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose. Other than as provided in this privacy policy, RMHC does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties.
RMHC reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a public safety matter.
Access
You are in control of all personal information you provide to us on-line. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us, you can let us know by contacting us.
Cookies
“Cookies” are pieces of information that an Internet site transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow a certain Internet site to remember important information that will make your use of the site more convenient. Like most Internet sites, RMHC uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your online experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our site on an anonymous, aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the site. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in that instance.
Use the options in your Internet browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the “Help” section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this Web site.
Links to Other Sites
We may offer links to sites that are not operated by RMHC. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
Our privacy policy became effective on July 22, 2004. From time to time, it may be necessary for RMHC to change its privacy policy, so we suggest that you check here periodically. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.
DONATE
VOLUNTEER
RESOURCES
PODCAST
Home
Ronald McDonald House
Our Mission
Stay
Donate
Wish List
Terms & Conditions
Privacy Policy
Contact Us
© 2018 McDonalds | Ronald McDonald House Charities Charlottesville
300 9th Street SW | Charlottesville, VA 22903
Office: (434) 295-1885 | Family Phone: (434) 295-6412 | Fax: (434) 295-7735
Ronald McDonald House Charities of Charlottesville is a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization. The following trademarks used herein are owned by McDonald's Corporation and its affiliates; McDonald's, Ronald McDonald House Charities, Ronald McDonald House Charities Logo, RMHC, Ronald McDonald House, Ronald McDonald Family Room, and Ronald McDonald Care Mobile.
